BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9)
1882-1949
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/009
132.5 cubic feet
129.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833613
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 18, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing (Food, Animal Food, Butchering, Bakeries, Beverage and Tobacco, Textile, Apparel, Leather, Footwear)
Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing (Wood, Paper, Petroleum, Chemical, Plastics, Rubber, Glass, Cement, Other Nonmetallic Mineral Products)
Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing (Metal, Machinery, Computer and Electronic, Electrical, Transportation Equipment, Furniture, Miscellaneous)
Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesalers
Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail
Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation
Series XII: Industry Code #49, Warehousing and Delivery Services
Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information (Publishing, Broadcasting, Communications, Libraries)
Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
Series XV: Industry Code #53, Real Estate and Rental and Leasing
Series XVI: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
Series XVII: Industry Code #56, Administration and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
Series XVIII: Industry Code # 61, Education
Series XIX: Industry Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
Series XX: Industry Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
Series XXI: Industry Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
Series XXII: Industry Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
Series XXIII: Industry Code #92, Public Administration
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Automobile industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Bakery employees -- United States; Collective labor agreements--Brewing industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Building trades -- United States.; Collective labor agreements-- Local transit -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Textile industry-- United States.; Collective labor agreements --Printing industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Shipbuilding industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Machinery industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements --Mining industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements-- Steel industry -- United States.; United States. Department of Labor - Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives; International Ladies' Garmernt Workers' Union -- Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; United Mine Workers of America -- Archives; United Steelworkers of America
5833613
- Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
  - Federal Labor Unions (agriculture), 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (logging), AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers, CIO, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers, CIO, 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Scope and Contents
    Some agreements marked as confidential
  - Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers, CIO, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Firemen and Oilers (logging), 1937-1938 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Seamen, 1931-1936 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing, Hunting, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Formerly Confidential
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing, Hunting, 1935-1937 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing, Hunting, 1940-1941 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Greenhouse, 1941-1944 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Fishery and Allied Workers, CIO, 1942-1945 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, 1938-1939 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Maritime Agreements - Fishermen's Unions, 1936-1938 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, 1934-1937 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 1 through 5, 1921-1933 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 6 through 10, 1928-1939 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - United Mine Workers, District 11, 1933-1939 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 12 and 13, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 14 through 17, 1935-1937 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 19 through 22, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - United Mine Workers, Districts 24 through 31, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - United Mine Workers, general, 1897-1939 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Operating Engineers (mining), 1936-1943 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (quarries), 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (mines), 1935-1939 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (mines), 1937-1939 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (mines), 1938-1940 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (mines), 1942 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - United Mine Workers (mines), 1935-1940 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Progressive Mine Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Oil Field, Gas Well, and Refinery Workers, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America, 1935-1939 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America, 1935-1939 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America - New England, 1931-1938 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America - Ohio-Wisconsin, 1933-1937 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America, 1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Quarry Workers' International Union of North America, 1939-1940 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Utility Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Utility Workers, CIO, PA, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Utility Workers, TN, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Utility Workers, 1937-1938 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Utility Workers, PA, RI, 1937-1938 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Utility Workers, CIO, WY, 1938-1940 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Mining, 1937-1939 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Mining (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Mining, 1935-1937 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Mining, 1940-1941 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1943, Mining, 1942-1943 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Mining, 1942-1944 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1945, Mining and Quarrying, 1944-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, Quarrying, 1941-1944 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, CIO, Mining, 1940-1945 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Mine Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Mine Workers, CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Mine Workers, 1937-1943 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Mine Workers, 1942-1944 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Mine Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Quarry Workers, CIO, 1939-1944 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Coal and Mining, 1937-1940 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Cuba Mining Company, 1941 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    Formerly confidential
- Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, utilities (CA, CO, and DC), 1934-1938 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, utilities (GA and IL), 1934-1939 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, utilities (IA, IN, KS, LA, ME, and MO), 1929-1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, utilities (MT, NY, OR, and OH), 1939-1937 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, utilities (TX, WA, and WI), 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Federal Labor Unions (utilities), 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Gas Workers Union
  - Utility Employees, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1936-1939 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1939 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1939 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1939 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1940 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1940 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1940 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1938-1941 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1937-1941 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1938-1941 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1939-1942 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (utilities), 1940-1942 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Operating Engineers (utilities), 1937-1940 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - United Mine Workers (utilities), 1933-1940 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Utilities, 1935-1939 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1943, Utilities, 1942-1943 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Utilities, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1945, Utilities, 1942-1945 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, Utilities, 1941-1944 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Utility Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1937-1943 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Power Generation, 1937-1940 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Utilities, 1941-1943 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Central New York Power Corporation, 1944 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Utilities, 1942-1945 (Box 129, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (CA and CO), 1913-1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (CT and DE), 1923-1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers and Pipe and Boiler Coverers Union (DC), 1916-1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (IL and IN), 1918-1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (IA and KY), 1926-1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (LA and MD), 1924-1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (MA), 1915-1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (MI and MN), 1917-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (MO), 1914-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (OH and OK), 1916-1936 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (NE and NJ), 1914-1932 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (NY), 1915-1937 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (OR and PA), 1906-1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (RI and TN), 1913-1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (TX and VA), 1917-1936 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers (WA and WI), 1913-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bill Posters, 1935-1937 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - United Brick and Clay Workers, 1930-1937 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    One agreement formerly confidential.
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (AL), 1914-1935 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Contains only constitutions and by-laws.
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (AR), 1914-1935 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (CT), 1905-1930 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (CA), 1919-1937 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (CO), 1916-1931 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (DC), 1905-1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (FL), 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Contains only constitution and by-laws.
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (GA), 1913-1933 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (IL), 1902-1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (IN), 1906-1937 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (IA), 1918-1938 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (KS), 1918-1920 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (KY), 1904-1935 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (LA), 1913-1935 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (ME), 1920-1935 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (MD), 1903-1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (MI), 1905-1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Documents in English and Italian
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (MS), 1904-1905 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (MA), 1903-1938 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (MO), 1905-1936 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (MN), 1909-1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (MT), 1917-1936 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (NE), 1917-1931 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (NH), 1914-1927 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (NJ), 1902-1935 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (NYC), 1906-1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (NY), 1905-1935 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (NY), 1903-1926 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (OH), 1912-1935 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (OH), 1913-1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (OK), 1904-1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (OR), 1913-1937 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (PA), 1902-1938 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (PA), 1906-1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (RI), 1913-1931 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (SC), 1923 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Contains no agreements
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (SD), 1903 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Contains only constitution and by-laws
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (TN), 1913-1936 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (TX), 1905-1937 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (UT), 1917-1920 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (VT), 1905 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (VA), 1917-1937 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (WA), 1905-1943 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers (WV), 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and other unions (WI), 1905-1938 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Documents in English and German.
  - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers and Paving Cutters' Union, 1910-1934 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers and Bricklayers and Stone Masons (AR, CA), 1921-1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (CO, CT, and DC), 1927-1936 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (FL, GA, and IL), 1903-1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (IN, IA, and KY), 1926-1933 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (LA, MA, and MI), 1928-1934 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (MN and MO), 1919-1931 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (MT and NE), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers and United Derrickment and Riggers (NY, OH), 1927-1936 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (OK, OR, and PA), 1924-1935 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (RI, TN, and TX), 1925-1935 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (UT, VA, and WA), 1920-1937 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (WV and WI), 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Building Trades Council (AZ and AR), 1918-1926 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Building Trades Council (CA), 1907-1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Building Trades Council (CO), 1920-1935 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Building Trades Council (CT), 1923-1927 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Building Trades Council (DC), 1919 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Contains only wage scales.
  - Building Trades Council (FL), 1905-1926 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Building Trades Council (ID), 1926-1932 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Building Trades Council and other unions (IL), 1912-1933 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Building Trades Council (IN), 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Building Trades Council (IA), 1906-1921 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Building Trades Council (MA), 1919-1926 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Building Trades Council (MI), 1920-1923 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Building Trades Council (MO), 1897-1934 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Building Trades Council (MT), 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Building Trades Council (NJ), 1904-1921 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Building Trades Council (NY), 1903-1932 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Building Trades Council (NV), 1925 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Building Trades Council (OH), 1902-1933 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Building Trades Council (OK), 1918-1926 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Building Trades Council (OR), 1920-1930 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Building Trades Council (PA) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Only contains wage scale.
  - Building Trades Council, AFL (TX), 1917-1934 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Building Trades Council (UT), 1922-1934 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Building Trades Council (WA), 1914-1934 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Building Trades Council (WV and WI), 1915-1937 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Building Trades Council and Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers, 1922-1936 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): AL, AZ, and AR, 1919-1938 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): CA, 1904-1937 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): CO, 1919-1933 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): CT, 1905-1933 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): DE and DC, 1916-1936 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Carpenters and Joiners: FL and GA, 1905-1935 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): IL, 1902-1937 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (general, construction): IL, 1893-1938 (Box 5, Folder 54)